/**
Questions Bank to shorten script.js code and increase efficency of site
**/

/*jshint esversion: 6 */

const questionBank = [{
        question: 'What happened in the 1914 Christmas Day truce during the First World War?',
        option: ['A game of football between British and German soldiers', 'English comrades did not quarrel', 'Pope Benedict XV has ascended to the papacy', 'Everyone had Coca Cola'],
        answer: 'A game of football between British and German soldiers'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which country annually sends a Christmas Tree to be erected in Londons Trafalgar Square?',
        option: ['Cananda', 'Denmark', 'Norway', 'Germany'],
        answer: 'Norway'
    },
    {
        question: 'What north-eastern US state holds the Guiness world record for largest Snowman?',
        option: ['Massachusetts', 'Rhode Island', 'Maine', 'New Hampshire'],
        answer: 'Maine'
    },
    {
        question: 'How many of Rudolphs eight companions names start with the letter D?',
        option: ['3', '1', '2', '4'],
        answer: '3'
    },
    {
        question: 'What do Americans leave for Santa on Christmas Eve?',
        option: ['Gift List', 'Baileys Irish Cream', 'Milk and Cookies', 'Sherry and Mince Pie'],
        answer: 'Milk and Cookies'
    },
    {
        question: 'In Home Alone, where are the McCallisters going on vacation when they leave Kevin behind?',
        option: ['London', 'Paris', 'New York', 'Milan'],
        answer: 'Paris'
    },
    {
        question: 'In what country did Silent Night originate?',
        option: ['Italy', 'England', 'Austria', 'Russia'],
        answer: 'Austria'
    },
    {
        question: 'The French word "Noel" is often used around Christmas, but what was its original meaning in Latin?',
        option: ['Night', 'Merry', 'Birth', 'New'],
        answer: 'Birth'
    },
    {
        question: 'What are you supposed to do when you find yourself under the mistletoe?',
        option: ['Kiss', 'Hug', 'Dance', 'Bow'],
        answer: 'Kiss'
    },
    {
        question: 'What gifts did The Three Wise Men give Jesus on his birthday?',
        option: ['Bread, Wine, and Diamond', 'Gold, Saphire, and Topaz', 'Gold, Frankincense, and Myrrh', 'Amber, Emerald, and Ruby'],
        answer: 'Gold, Frankincense, and Myrrh'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which ocean can Christmas Island be found in?',
        option: ['Indian', 'Pacific', 'Atlantic', 'Arctic'],
        answer: 'Indian'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the best selling Christmas single of all time in the UK?',
        option: ['Bing Crosby - White Christmas', 'Band Aid - Do They Know its Christmas?', 'Mariah Carey - All I want for Christmas is you', 'Wham! - Last Christmas'],
        answer: 'Band Aid - Do They Know its Christmas?'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which Christmas decoration do the Royal Family not have on their trees?',
        option: ['Lights', 'Baubles', 'An Angel', 'Tinsel'],
        answer: 'Tinsel'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the most popular meal for Christmas in Japan?',
        option: ['Roast Turkey', 'KFC Fried Chicken', 'Turkey Ramen', 'Sushi'],
        answer: 'KFC Fried Chicken'
    },
    {
        question: 'In which year was the first Christmas card sent?',
        option: ['1925', '1890', '1912', '1843'],
        answer: '1843'
    }
];